export const QuizData = [
    {
      id:1,
      question: 'Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?',
      options: ['Virtual DOM', 'Real DOM', 'Both', 'None'],
      answer: 'Virtual DOM'
    },
    {  id:2,
      question: 'What is ReactJS?',
      options: ['Client-side Library', 'Server-side Library', 'Both', 'None'],
      answer: 'Client-side Library'
    },
    {   id:3,
        question: 'Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside?',
        options: ['Setstate', 'Props', 'Rendering', 'Babel'],
        answer: 'Props'
      },
      { id:4,
        question: 'Who created React.js?',
        options: ['Google', 'Accenture', 'Adobe','Facebook'],
        answer: 'Facebook'
      },
      { id:5,
        question: 'In which language is React.js written?',
        options: ['Python', 'Javascript', 'PHP', 'Java'],
        answer: 'Javascript'
      },
      { id:6,
        question: 'What is Babel?',
        options: ['Js Compiler', 'Js Transpiler', 'Js Interpreter', 'None'],
        answer: 'Js Compiler'
      },
      { id:7,
        question: 'Identify the command used to create a react app globally?',
        options: ['npm install create-react-app', 'npm install -g create-react-app', 'npm -g create-react-app', 'npx create-react-app'],
        answer: 'npm install -g create-react-app'
      },
      { id:8,
        question: 'A state in React.js is also known as?',
        options: ['Internal Storage', 'External Storage', 'Static Storage', 'None'],
        answer: 'Internal Storage'
      },
      { id:9,
        question: 'State whether true or false:  Props are methods into other components?',
        options: ['True', 'False'],
        answer: 'True'
      },
      { id:10,
        question: 'In MVC, what does React.js act as?',
        options: ['Model', 'View', 'Controller', 'Middleware'],
        answer: 'View'
      },
    
  ];